{
    "id": "706d046e89884fb0a8fe37ea80ad3382",
    "title": "Adjectives And Adverbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Please do it …………………….",
            "description": "Here we use the adverb quickly to modify the verb do.",
            "answers": [
                "quick",
                "quickly"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He ran as …………………… as he could.",
            "description": "Fast can be an adjective or adverb.",
            "answers": [
                "fast",
                "fastly"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I am not ……………………. interested in this offer.",
            "description": "Much can be used as an adverb meaning very. ",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "many",
                "most"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She walked with ……………………. difficulty.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "many",
                "most"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She spoke …………………….. anything.",
            "description": "Hardly means scarcely. ",
            "answers": [
                "hard",
                "hardly"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I was ……………………… inside the house when the kids started yelling.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hard",
                "hardly"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We ………………….. see elephants in cities.",
            "description": "Hardly ever means very rarely.",
            "answers": [
                "hardly",
                "rarely",
                "hardly ever"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "It was a ……………………. occurrence.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "rare",
                "rarely",
                "scarce"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The students are …………………… waiting for the results.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "anxious",
                "anxiously"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "It happened all of a ……………………….",
            "description": "All of a sudden and suddenly mean the same. ",
            "answers": [
                "sudden",
                "suddenly"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I was …………………….. to hear the news.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "eager",
                "eagerly"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We …………………… listened to his anecdotes.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "eager",
                "eagerly"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}